lrngo.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy for LRNGO.com Users

LRNGO, INC. and its affiliates (hereinafter "LRNGO" or "Company" or collectively, “we” or “us or “our”) consider the personal information of all people who use our website www.LRNGO.com (hereinafter "LRNGO" or “Website”) very important, and therefore we have the following Privacy Policy.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy and protection of all persons who provide their personal data to LRNGO. This Privacy Notice describes the ways we may collect information from and about you, and what we do with the information we collect, so that you may make an informed decision about what information you are willing to provide.

By visiting LRNGO.com or otherwise providing your personal information to LRNGO via any other means, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the term “visitor” or “user” includes both those who are and those who are not current customers, and both those who are and those who are not paying customers, whether you upload information to our website, download it, or are merely visiting our website, as well as those who interact with us through other means, including other online services (e.g., e-mail, chat), by phone, text messages, fax, by written correspondence, or in person.

You can choose not to provide certain information when using or interacting with LRNGO, but as a result, in some instances, you might not be able to take advantage of LRNGO’s features.

  1. Personal Information Collected
  2. Use of Personal Information Collected
  3. Location, Retention, Period of Use and Disposal of Personal Information
  4. Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties
  5. User Control of Personal Information 
  6. Personal Information Security Guidance
  7. Inquiries or Complaints
  8. Changes in Privacy Policy

### 1\. Personal Information Collected

In the process of using the service, IP address, cookies, service usage history and device information may be generated and collected. Personal information collected from users at the time of visiting LRNGO is as follows:

When you visit our Website, our server logs your IP address (unique network address), the time and duration of your visit, and the time and duration of your visit to the specific website pages you view. IP address, cookies, service usage history and device information may be generated and collected. If you arrive at our website by clicking a search engine result (paid or unpaid), a link from another website, or a link in an email, we may capture information that tracks your visit from that link. We may also capture information about your computer system, such as your browser type and operating system.

Cookies

We may place a cookie on your hard drive during the web visit. A cookie is a unique identifier that we use to help us identify the number of unique visitors to our website, as well as repeat visitors, and the source of the visits. Other servers cannot read them and personal information cannot be gathered from them. They are simply an identifier shared between you and us to allow us to improve the services we offer to you through our website and allow us to identify which webpages are being used.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. If you do not wish cookies to be placed on your computer, they can be disabled in your web browser. The option to do so is normally found in your browser’s “security settings” section. However, please note that declining or permanently disabling cookies in your browser may hinder your experience and use of LRNGO and prevent you from taking full advantage of the website, as well as hinder your internet experience with other websites and interactive services.

Membership Signup

The following personal information is collected from users who voluntarily choose to create a profile and become members at the time of membership sign up:

Required - email address, password, city and country information, name or screen name.

Optional - full name, location information, phone number, picture, resume.

Membership Use

Personal information collected from member users during service use is as follows:

Personal information and preferences may be collected from users by LRNGO during individual service use, including communications and interactions with other users, and during payment processes.

In the processing of payments to other users or to LRNGO, the following payment information may be collected through third party processors:

  * PayPal Payment: PayPal account ID, etc.
  * Stripe Payment: Stripe account ID, etc.
  * Credit card Payment: Credit card company name, credit card number, etc.

Personal Information Received From Users In European Union Countries

LRNGO’s processing of personal information from individuals in European countries is:

  * occasional,
  * does not include, on a large scale, processing of special categories of data like racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs or processing of personal data relating to criminal convictions and offences, and
  * is unlikely to result in a risk to the rights and freedoms of natural persons, taking into account the nature, context, scope and purposes of the processing.

Regardless, LRNGO’s Privacy Policy follows practices set forth in the EU Privacy Shield guidelines regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States, and LRNGO will certify to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern and LRNGO will take all reasonable steps to comply. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit www.privacyshield.gov.

Under the Privacy Shield framework, LRNGO has the responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. LRNGO will remain liable under Privacy Shield if any of its agents process such personal information from EU countries in a manner that is inconsistent with Privacy Shield unless LRNGO can show that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

In compliance with Privacy Shield Principles, LRNGO commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy should first contact LRNGO at:

ATTN: Compliance Management  
compliance@lrngo.com  
US +1.832.362.1787

As a last resort for complaints, individuals may be able to invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel, which consists of a pool of arbitrators designated by the Department of Commerce and the European commission. Parties to this arbitration can select either one or three arbitrators for the binding arbitration.

Sensitive Information

We will not intentionally collect or maintain, and do not want you to provide, any information regarding your medical or health condition, race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or other sensitive information.

Children's Online Privacy Protection

LRNGO is not designed for or directed to children under the age of 18, and our Terms of Use prohibit users under the age of 18 from using our website. Therefore, we will not intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 18 at any time for any reason. If you believe or suspect that our Terms have been breached and we have unintentionally collected the personal information of a child or user under the age of 18, please contact us at compliance@lrngo.com immediately so that we may delete it.

Links To Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over those other websites. The privacy policies of those websites may differ from LRNGO practices and are not controlled by LRNGO or covered by this Privacy Policy. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. We do not make any representations about third-party websites, and we encourage you to review their privacy policies before using those sites or submitting your personal data.

Public Information

While using our Website, at your option, you will have opportunities to post personal information in public areas. Please understand that when you post such information, it is made public and is not subject to this policy. We are not responsible for any third party’s use of personal information you elect to publicly disclose through our Website or service.

The personal information you elect to post on your profile if you choose to become a member is fully visible to other members, users and customers of our Website and services. The personal information you voluntarily elect to post publicly on your profile may also be visible to others on or off of our Website (e.g., users of third- party search engines). Excerpts from your profile may appear on the services of others (e.g., search engine results, etc.), and old/past profile information you have voluntarily entered may remain on these services until they update their data cache with any changes you have made to your profile. Your settings, how much personal information you elect to show (to members and publicly), the degree of connection or interests you have, the subscriptions other users may have, their usage, and other variables impact the availability of your profile and whether other users or visitors can view certain fields in your profile. You are responsible for all of your choices and the accuracy and all updates regarding the personal information you post.

If you choose to write and submit an article or a post a comment publicly on LRNGO, it can be viewed by everyone and re-shared anywhere. Members, visitors and others will be able to find and see your publicly-shared content, including your screen name or name if you have provided one.

### 2\. Use of Personal Information Collected

LRNGO uses personal information only for membership management, service development, provision and improvement, maintaining a safe internet-use environment for our users, and the following purposes:

Personal information is used for identity verification, purchase and payment, and delivery of services when a user is provided with paid premium services.

Personal information is used for maintaining a history of services and for frequency analysis and statistics on service use, and other service analysis and statistics.

Personal information is used to build and maintain a safe service environment, so that users can use LRNGO safely in the context of security, privacy, and minimal risk.

Personal information is used for marketing and promotional purposes such as providing event information, participation opportunities, and advertisement information.

LRNGO may use your personal information to process your service requests, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders and preferences, provide access to secure areas of the Website, recommend products or services that might be of interest to you, personalize your visit to our website, and to review, develop and continually improve the services we provide online. We may also use this information to prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Website and to enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

We limit the use of personal information to the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy and for which the individual has provided implicit or explicit consent.

### 3\. Location, Retention, Period of Use and Disposal of Personal Information

LRNGO holds your personal information on servers located in the U.S. If you choose to provide us with your information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States. The information we collect is subject to U.S. state and federal law. If you are accessing LRNGO from other jurisdictions, please be advised that you are transferring your personal information to us in the United States. The server host’s role is limited to providing a hosting and storage service to LRNGO and to provide the necessary level of protection for the data stored. If you do not want your personal information to be transferred to a server located in the U.S., you should not provide LRNGO with your personal information or use the Website.

We retain personal information for only as long as necessary to fulfill the stated use purposes in this Privacy Policy or as required by law or regulations and thereafter appropriately dispose of such information. If we have obtained a separate consent from a user regarding the personal information retention period or law imposes the obligation to keep the information for a certain period, the personal information will be kept safely during that period.

When the purpose of collection and use of personal information has been achieved– as in the case of the withdrawal of membership, the end of service, or the voluntary request of a member to delete personal information originally provided by the user, the personal information is disposed of in a way that cannot be recovered. The information that has a certain retention period imposed on by the law shall also be permanently disposed of after all stated use purposes in this Privacy Policy have been fulfilled and after the expiration date.

### 4\. Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

LRNGO does not provide user personal information to third parties without prior consent of the user. However, LRNGO provides personal information only when the user directly agrees to providing personal information in order to use products or services of the external affiliate, and when the user is obliged to submit personal information in accordance with the relevant laws and regulations. Personal information we gather is for internal use only and LRNGO will not authorize the release of this information to anyone outside LRNGO (except to third party service providers to who perform functions on our behalf but in such event personal information will only be shared to the extent reasonably necessary to perform their functions and they will not be authorized to use it for any other function), unless you have consented to such disclosure.

If you breach our website terms of use, or if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, such as a lawful request from public authorities in regard to law enforcement or national security requirements, we may disclose your information to a relevant authority. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and security or credit risk. In other words, we may release the information we collect to third parties when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce our legal rights, to protect the rights and safety of others, or to assist with industry efforts to control fraud, spam or other undesirable conduct.

We may release the information we collect to a third party if the information is provided to enable the third party to provide services to us, provided that the third party has agreed to use at least the same level of privacy protections described in this Privacy Policy, and is permitted to use the information only for the purpose of providing services to us. All communications of personal information to third parties will be done in a manner consistent with applicable laws and regulations, as well as our internal information security and Privacy Policy.

### 5\. User Control of Personal Information 

Right to Access Your Personal Information

You have the right to access your personal data. In most cases, you can control and access your personal information on LRNGO at any time yourself. If you need assistance and believe that any personal information we have about you is incorrect, or is, has been, or might be used inappropriately, please contact us at compliance@lrngo.com, and we will take steps to correct or delete the information, or restrict its use, as appropriate.

Users who have created a profile on LRNGO may permanently delete all of their personal information at any time for any reason by logging in and clicking on Personal Settings under their picture, and then clicking on Remove My Profile at the bottom of the page.

Users who have created a profile on LRNGO may modify, delete, or change some or all of their personal information at any time for any reason by logging in and clicking on Edit My Profile under their picture. Changes will not be permanent until you click the Save button at the bottom of the third page (Step 3 page). Modifications and changes must comply with our Terms of Use, as well as local and international laws.

Opting Out of Communications

You may choose to opt-out of receiving communications from any LRNGO user at any time for any reason by logging in and clicking on My Messages, then clicking on a message from the user you wish to cease communications with, and then clicking on Mark as Spam.

You may choose to opt-out of receiving communications from all LRNGO users permanently at any time for any reason by logging in and clicking on Personal Settings, and then clicking on Remove My Profile at the bottom of the page.

You may choose to opt-out of receiving communications from LRNGO (except as necessary to provide services for which you have voluntarily opted-in or paid, or for meeting applicable legal requirements or permitting third party service providers who perform functions on our behalf as described in section 4 of this Privacy Policy), including your opting out of receiving future email correspondence. We will not use your contact information to correspond with you about our services if you are not using those opt-in services and you ask us not to. Please send your request to compliance@lrngo.com or write us at ATTN: Compliance Management, LRNGO, INC., 800 Wilcrest Dr., Suite #258, Houston TX 77042. Please note that it may take up to fifteen working days to remove your contact information from our communications lists, so you may receive correspondence from us for a short time after you make your request.

### 6\. Personal Information Security Guidance

LRNGO is committed to commercially reasonable safeguards, best practices, and approaches to keep your information secure and prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information in our possession. We use various security measures to protect the information we collect, as appropriate to the type of information, including encryption, firewalls, and access controls. We store information you provide to us on a computer system located in a controlled facility with limited access and our company databases are accessible only by LRNGO. However, while we make reasonable efforts to prevent third party, non-affiliate access to personally identifiable information, all data transmission over the Internet is not 100% secure, and information disclosed online can potentially be collected and used, illegally or otherwise, by those other than the intended recipients. Therefore, despite these safeguards, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to our Website, or guarantee that information on our website will not be improperly accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. In view of the foregoing, we cannot guarantee or warrant that your personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to or accessed by parties other than those authorized under this Privacy Policy.

We use reasonable measures to safeguard the security and integrity of your personal information through procedures and technology designed for that purpose. You should always safeguard your own personal information by protecting any passwords or other identifying information used to access your account with us and by safely disposing of any personal information that is no longer needed.

Verification

LRNGO, INC. utilizes the self-assessment approach to assure its compliance with its Privacy Policy. LRNGO regularly verifies that the Privacy Policy is accurate, comprehensive, and prominently displayed, and conducts its self-assessment periodically to ensure that all relevant privacy practices are being followed. Internal procedures for periodically conducting objective reviews of compliance are in place.

Communication

Individuals are informed that their personal information is: 

  * used only for the purposes identified in the Privacy Policy and only if the individual has provided implicit or explicit consent, unless a law or regulation specifically requires otherwise,
  * retained for no longer than necessary to fulfill the stated purposes, or for a period specifically required by law or regulation, and
  * disposed of in a manner reasonably intended to prevent loss, theft, misuse, or unauthorized access.

### 7\. Inquiries or Complaints

LRNGO has designated both a data protection officer and also a manager who would respond to inquiries and complaints related to personal information. If you have a question or complaint about this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact us at compliance@lrngo.com or write to us at:

LRNGO, INC.  
ATTN: Compliance Management  
800 Wilcrest, Suite #258  
Houston, TX 77042

We will investigate the matter and are committed to resolve any privacy concerns that you may have. Should any dispute or controversy arise out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, our website, or related services provided by us (with the possible exception of specific agreements with customers regarding products or services governed by the terms and conditions of LRNGO, INC.), it shall be subject to the jurisdiction and venue of State and Federal Courts in Harris County, Texas, and shall be governed by the laws of the State of Texas without regard to its conflict of law provisions. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed and you are a visitor located in the EU, you may contact European Data Protection Authorities.

If any portion of this Privacy Policy is deemed void or unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this Privacy Policy and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions. In addition, please note that LRNGO, INC. is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission.

### 8\. Changes in Privacy Policy

Our website changes constantly and our Privacy Policy may also change from time to time. You should check our website frequently to see recent changes; however, our priority moving forward will be to protect each individual’s personal information, and we will never materially change our Privacy Policy without user consent in a way that is inconsistent with that priority.

In the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of all or substantially all of its assets, or sale of an individual website owned by LRNGO, LRNGO may transfer your personal information to a third party as a part of such merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale. In such an event, we will require such third party to honor our current Privacy Policy, until or unless the third party provides you with notice of changes to the Privacy Policy and permits you to exercise any rights you may have under applicable laws to limit disclosures of information about you.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 25th, 2018.
